Morning.
早晨。
Hi.
你好。
Oh, how was your date last night?
噢，昨晚的約會怎麼樣？
Pretty good.
不錯。
Oh, good.
哦，很好。
Ah!
啊!
My God, sorry.
天哪，對不起。
Okay, really good.
好吧，真的很好。
Anyway, I gotta go.
無論如何，我得走了。
I'm late for work.
我上班遲到了。
What?
什麼？
You're gonna leave this person with me?
你要把這個人留給我嗎？
Yeah, hey, don't worry.
是的，嘿，別擔心。
She's a terrific girl.
她是一個很棒的女孩。
And hey, listen, you do me a favor.
嘿，聽著，你幫我一個忙。
When she comes out, could you just mention that I'm not looking for
當她出來的時候，你能告訴我我不是在找嗎？
a serious relationship?
認真的關係？
That'd be great.
那太好了。
What?
什麼？
Are you kidding?
你在開玩笑吧？
Just casually slip it in, you know?
隨便塞進去就知道了？
Lay the groundwork.
奠定基礎。
Tell her, uh, I'm a loner.
告訴她，呃，我是個孤獨的人。
No, an outlaw.
不，是亡命之徒。
She doesn't want to get mixed up with the likes of me.
她不想跟我這樣的人混在一起。
You know what?
你知道嗎？
That's a lot to remember.
有很多需要記住的事情。
Can't I just tell her that you're a pig?
我就不能直接告訴她你是豬嗎？
Hey, I'm gonna call her later myself.
嘿，我稍後會親自打電話給她。
Honest.
誠實的。
But come on, Chandler used to do it.
但得了吧，錢德勒以前就這麼做過。
He'd even make the girl pancakes.
他甚至會給女孩做煎餅。
Plus, he'd make extras and leave them for me.
另外，他還會做一些額外的東西，然後留給我。
Well, forget it.
好吧，算了。
I'm not telling that girl anything.
我不會告訴那個女孩任何事。
That is not my responsibility.
那不是我的責任。
Fine.
美好的。
Now, where'd we land on those pancakes?
現在，我們在哪裡找到那些煎餅了？
Hi.
你好。
Sorry about that, but I didn't get that lock to work on the
抱歉，但我沒能在該裝置上使用該鎖
door.
門。
Yeah, Joey kind of disabled it when I moved in.
是的，當我搬進來時，喬伊就禁用了它。
You must be Rachel.
你一定是雷切爾。
I'm Erin.
我是艾琳。
Hi.
你好。
I don't mean this to sound like high school, but did he say
我的意思並不是說這聽起來像高中，但他是說嗎
anything about me?
有什麼關於我的嗎？
Would you like some pancakes?
您想要一些煎餅嗎？
Come on.
快點。
Why are we here?
我們為什麼在這裡？
Okay, okay.
好吧，好吧。
Take a guess.
猜猜看。
The hot chicks?
辣妹們？
Okay, okay.
好吧，好吧。
I was typing names into the library computer earlier.
我早些時候正在圖書館的電腦上輸入名字。
You know, for fun.
你知道，為了好玩。
And I typed mine in, and guess what came up?
我輸入了我的內容，猜猜會發生什麼事？
My doctoral dissertation.
我的博士論文。
It's here.
就在這裡。
Yeah, right.
是的，對。
It's right down here in the biggest library in the university.
它就在大學最大的圖書館。
Oh, that's actually pretty cool.
哦，這實際上很酷。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, um, there's also a book here by a woman named Wendy Vagina.
哦，嗯，這裡還有一本書，作者是一位名叫 Wendy Vagina 的女士。
What is that?
那是什麼？
Sounds like two people are really enjoying the Dewey Decimal System.
聽起來兩個人真的很喜歡杜威十進位制。
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉。
You didn't bring me here to do that, did you?
你帶我來這裡不是為了這麼做的，對嗎？
She sent the chicken back again?
她又把雞送回來了？
She said it's too dry now, and she wants to come back here
她說現在太乾了，她想回到這裡
and explain to you exactly how she wants.
並向你準確地解釋她想要什麼。
Well, fine.
好吧，好吧。
I'd like to meet this chicken expert.
我想見見這位養雞專家。
Send the colonel in.
派上校進來。
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
Lucky bastard.
幸運的混蛋。
Janice, how are you, Miss Hot Shot Chef at the big, fancy restaurant
珍妮絲，你好嗎，這家豪華大餐廳的主廚小姐
with the best chicken ever?
最好的雞肉？
I'm fine.
我很好。
Oh, what is that on your finger?
哦，你手指上的是什麼？
I'm blind!
我瞎了！
Somebody's been doing a little cooking outside the restaurant.
有人在餐廳外做飯。
So, who's the lucky guy?
那麼，誰是幸運兒呢？
Sorry.
對不起。
Um, funny story.
嗯，有趣的故事。
Hey, what's up?
嘿，怎麼了？
Hey.
嘿。
Hey, who's your friend?
嘿，誰是你的朋友？
Hey!
嘿！
Hey, Jeremy.
嘿，傑裡米。
Erin.
艾琳。
You're still here.
你還在這裡。
Yeah, we ended up spending the day together and had such a great
是的，我們最終在一起度過了一天，度過了一段美好的時光
time.
時間。
Why wouldn't you?
為什麼不呢？
Erin is great.
艾琳很棒。
And then there's you guys.
然後就是你們了。
I better get going.
我最好走了。
Today was great, babe.
今天很棒，寶貝。
I know.
我知道。
Okay.
好的。
And Joey.
還有喬伊。
Last night was fun.
昨晚很有趣。
Yeah.
是的。
I'll call you.
我會打電話給你。
Oh, and I'll call you, too.
哦，我也會打電話給你。
Or I'll call you.
或者我打電話給你。
And call me.
並打電話給我。
Hey, look at that.
嘿，看看那個。
We're all going to call each other.
我們都會互相打電話。
Okay, good to see you again.
好的，很高興再次見到你。
Bye.
再見。
Bye-bye.
Bye.
再見。
So, system kind of broke down, huh?
那麼，系統有點崩潰了，對吧？
Oh, Joey, I'm sorry.
哦，喬伊，對不起。
I just couldn't tell her all those things you wanted me to tell
我只是無法告訴她你想讓我告訴的所有事情
her.
她。
And, you know, we got to talking and...
而且，你知道，我們必須談談......
We want you to marry her.
我們希望你娶她。
What?
什麼？
She is so amazing.
她太棒了。
You have no idea.
你不知道。
No idea?
不知道嗎？
Who do you think brought her here?
你認為是誰帶她來這裡的？
Cupid.
丘位元。
Joey, she's so cool.
喬伊，她太酷了。
She speaks four languages.
她會說四種語言。
Man, do you know what guys want?
男人，你知道男人想要什麼嗎？
Look, Joey, come on.
聽著，喬伊，來吧。
She's so perfect for you.
她對你來說是如此完美。
I mean, she's sweet.
我的意思是，她很可愛。
She likes baseball.
她喜歡棒球。
And she had two beers at lunch.
午餐時她喝了兩瓶啤酒。
My beers?
我的啤酒？
Look, you guys, she's a very nice girl, okay?
你們看，她是個非常好的女孩，好嗎？
We had a good time.
我們玩得很開心。
But I don't see it going anywhere.
但我認為它不會有任何進展。
Yeah, but you always say that.
是的，但你總是這麼說。
Yeah, maybe if you gave this girl a chance, it would go somewhere.
是的，也許如果你給這個女孩一個機會，它會有所收穫。
Look, I'm sorry, you guys.
聽著，我很抱歉，你們。
I just don't think so.
我只是不這麼認為。
Whatever.
任何。
Fine.
美好的。
Hey, don't start judging me.
嘿，別開始評斷我。
Huh?
啊？
You're the one who's in love with her assistant.
你是那個愛上她助理的人。
And you, you're the one who's having the affair with the guy who
而你，你就是那個跟那個男人有染的人
keeps the pigeons on the roof.
把鴿子養在屋頂上。
Secret affair.
秘密戀情。
What did I say?
我說什麼了？
Hey.
嘿。
Hey, cutie cutie.
嘿嘿，小可愛。
So, uh, I ran into someone you know today at work.
所以，呃，我今天在工作中遇到了一個你認識的人。
Oh, yeah?
哦，是嗎？
Who was it?
是誰？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I am so sorry, sweetie.
我很抱歉，親愛的。
Are you okay?
你還好嗎？
You didn't tell her we're getting married, did you?
你沒有告訴她我們要結婚了，是嗎？
Well, she saw the ring.
好吧，她看到了戒指。
Did she freak out?
她嚇壞了嗎？
Well, she was shocked when I told her, but then again, so were
好吧，當我告訴她時，她很震驚，但話又說回來，我也很震驚
most people.
大多數人。
Well, she actually has a boyfriend, you know, herself.
好吧，她實際上有一個男朋友，你知道，她自己。
His name's Clark.
他的名字叫克拉克。
She also kind of invited herself to her wedding.
她也邀請自己參加她的婚禮。
Clark, too.
克拉克也是。
You said no, right?
你說不是吧？
Huh?
啊？
You said no, right?
你說不是吧？
Well, she cornered me.
好吧，她把我逼到牆角了。
She asked me if the wedding was in town.
她問我婚禮是否在城裡舉行。
I mean, what was I supposed to do?
我的意思是，我該做什麼？
Lie!
說謊！
How hard is that?
那有多難？
Your check's in the mail.
您的支票已寄出。
Oh, your baby is so cute.
哦，你的寶寶真可愛。
I can't wait to read your book, Ross.
我迫不及待地想讀你的書，羅斯。
Come on.
快點。
So she comes to the wedding.
於是她就來參加婚禮了。
I didn't think it would be so bad.
我沒想到會這麼糟。
What, do you think she's just gonna sit there quietly?
怎麼，你以為她會安靜地坐在那裡嗎？
You don't think she's gonna want to make a toast?
你不認為她會想要敬酒嗎？
You don't think she's gonna want to grab the microphone and sing part
你認為她不會想要拿起麥克風來唱歌
-time lover?
-時間情人？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
She's not gonna like the chicken that night, either, is she?
她也不會喜歡那天晚上的雞肉，對嗎？
You know what?
你知道嗎？
It's gonna be okay.
會沒事的。
You know what?
你知道嗎？
She's probably not gonna even want to come.
她可能根本不想來。
Really?
真的嗎？
No.
不。
That was a lie.
那是一個謊言。
See how easy that was?
看看那是多麼容易嗎？
So...
所以...
You would have just lied?
你剛剛會說謊嗎？
Yes.
是的。
Would it have really been that easy?
事情真的那麼容易嗎？
Yes.
是的。
Good.
好的。
So do it Saturday night, because we're going to dinner with her and
所以星期六晚上就這樣做吧，因為我們要跟她一起吃晚餐
Clark.
克拉克.
Nah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah!
啊啊啊啊啊啊啊！
Hi.
你好。
What's wrong?
怎麼了？
People are doing it in front of my book!
人們在我的書前這樣做！
I'm sorry?
對不起？
My doctoral dissertation is in the library at school.
我的博士論文在學校的圖書館。
I went to see it, and there were students making babies right in
我去看了，裡面有學生在生孩子
the middle of the paleontology section!
古生物學部分的中間！
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
Did you get to see anything good?
有看到什麼好東西嗎？
That is not the point.
這不是重點。
I know that's not the point.
我知道這不是重點。
I'm trying to make it the point.
我正在努力強調這一點。
Let me ask you something.
讓我問你一件事。
At your school, was there, uh, like a place on campus where students
在你們學校，呃，就像校園裡學生們聚集的地方一樣
went to to fool around?
去鬼混了？
Yeah, there was.
是的，有。
In the corner of the library, where all these dusty books were that
在圖書館的角落裡，那些滿是灰塵的書都放在那裡
nobody ever read, yes, there was.
沒有人讀過，是的，有。
Great.
偉大的。
Because people kept showing up.
因為人們不斷出現。
I think it's like a thing.
我覺得這就像一件事。
Now, hold on a second.
現在，請稍等。
Fifth floor against that back wall?
五樓靠著後牆？
Oh, for crying out loud!
噢，大聲哭出來！
Huh?
啊？
All right, so we should go catch our movie.
好吧，我們該去看電影了。
Well, now, what's the rush?
好吧，現在急什麼？
I'd like to see the previews.
我想看預覽。
The candy.
糖果。
Oh, hey.
哦，嘿。
Well, look who's here.
好吧，看看誰在這裡。
Hey, Joey.
嘿，喬伊。
Hey, Erin.
嘿，艾琳。
Hey, Rachel.
嘿，雷切爾。
Hi.
你好。
Well, we were just about to take off and see a movie.
好吧，我們正準備起飛去看電影。
Oh, no!
哦，不！
What's wrong?
怎麼了？
Oh, Phoebe.
哦，菲比。
We forgot that party we have to go to.
我們忘記了我們要去參加的那個聚會。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
What party?
什麼派對？
A birthday party.
生日聚會。
Whose birthday party?
誰的生日派對？
Allison's birthday party.
艾莉森的生日派對。
Oh.
哦。
And how old is Allison?
艾莉森多大了？
32.
I feel so terrible ditching you like this.
像這樣拋棄你我感覺很糟。
No, that's okay.
不，沒關係。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
Why don't you guys do something?
你們為什麼不做點什麼？
Look how that worked out.
看看效果如何。
If you want, do you want to catch a movie?
如果你願意的話，你想看電影嗎？
Yeah, sure, that'd be fun.
是的，當然，那會很有趣。
I guess I'll talk to you guys after Allison's party.
我想艾莉森的派對結束後我會和你們談談。
Oh, yeah, that actually might go late.
哦，是的，那實際上可能會晚一些。
I'll wait up.
我會等一下。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
Hi, I'm a professor here.
你好，我是這裡的教授。
Do you know the paleontology section, fifth floor, stack 437?
你知道五樓437號棧古生物區嗎？
Well, yes.
嗯，是的。
Just give me five minutes.
給我五分鐘。
I just have to find someone to cover my shift.
我只需要找個人來代替我輪班。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
Can I speak to someone in charge, please?
我可以和負責人通話嗎？
How can I help you?
我怎麼幫你？
Hi, I was wondering, is it possible to increase security in the paleontology
你好，我想知道是否有可能提高古生物學的安全性
section?
部分？
See, I wrote a book that's up there, and instead of reading it,
看，我寫了一本書，上面有，但我沒有讀它，
people are, well, they're rolling around in front of it.
人們，好吧，他們在它前面打滾。
We are aware of the problem you're referring to.
我們知道您提到的問題。
But as far as increasing security, I'm afraid the library is very understaffed.
但就加強安全性而言，恐怕圖書館人手嚴重不足。
I can't help you.
我幫不了你。
Well, fine.
好吧，好吧。
Fine.
美好的。
If I'm the only person with any appreciation of the sanctity of the
如果我是唯一一個欣賞神聖事物的人
written word, then I'll go up there and defend it myself.
書寫文字，然後我會親自去那裡捍衛它。
Don't you follow me.
你別跟著我。
Hey.
嘿。
How did it go with Aaron?
亞倫的事怎麼樣了？
Unbelievable.
難以置信。
We had the best time.
我們度過了最美好的時光。
Yay!
耶！
Oh, so you're not mad at us anymore.
哦，所以你不再生我們的氣了。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
You guys are totally right.
你們是完全正確的。
This was so much better than the first time we went out.
這比我們第一次出去好多了。
You know, that was so awkward.
你知道，那太尷尬了。
We were both really nervous.
我們都很緊張。
Didn't you sleep together?
你們沒一起睡嗎？
Yeah, that really calms me down.
是的，這確實讓我平靜下來。
Oh.
哦。
And we have so much in common.
我們有很多共同點。
She loves sandwiches, sports, although she is a MET fan.
儘管她是 MET 粉絲，但她喜歡三明治和運動。
Not much of an issue now, but if we were ever to have
現在不是什麼大問題，但如果我們曾經有過
kids...
孩子們...
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Listen to you talking about having kids.
聽你說起生孩子的事。
Oh, my Joey.
哦，我的喬伊。
Oh, please don't get married before I do.
哦，請不要在我結婚前結婚。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦，哦，哦。
Oh, I just cannot believe that Clark stood me up.
哦，我簡直不敢相信克拉克竟然放我鴿子。
He may still show up.
他可能還會出現。
Oh, what are you, stupid?
哦，你是什麼，傻瓜？
It's been three hours.
已經三個小時了。
Is that all?
這就是全部嗎？
I just feel like such a fool.
我只是覺得自己像個傻瓜。
You know, I really, I thought this guy was my soulmate.
你知道，我真的，我認為這個人是我的靈魂伴侶。
But I was your soulmate.
但我是你的靈魂伴侶。
What am I doing?
我在做什麼？
Oh, you know, let's just, oh, let's forget about Clark.
哦，你知道，讓我們，哦，讓我們忘記克拉克。
Let's just go on to happier things, okay?
讓我們繼續做更快樂的事吧？
Um, why don't you tell me about your lovely wedding?
嗯，為什麼不告訴我你可愛的婚禮呢？
Well, actually, uh, there was something that we wanted to tell you about
嗯，實際上，呃，我們想告訴你一些事情
the wedding.
婚禮。
Um, it's going to be a small ceremony.
嗯，這將是一個小型儀式。
Uh, tiny.
呃，很小。
We're not even sure why we're having it.
我們甚至不確定為什麼會這樣。
It's actually going to be just family.
事實上，這只是一家人。
Oh, wait.
哦，等等。
You two think of me as family?
你們兩個把我當家人嗎？
Oh, I have to ask you something now and be honest.
哦，我現在必須問你一件事，而且要誠實。
Do you want me to sing Careless Whisper or Lady in Red?
你想讓我唱《粗心細語》或《紅衣女郎》嗎？
How can you say that?
你怎麼能這麼說呢？
The Mets have no closer.
大都會隊沒有更接近的機會。
What about Benitez?
貝尼特斯呢？
What about Game 1 of the series?
該系列的第一場比賽怎麼樣？
What about Shut Up?
閉嘴怎麼樣？
You shut up.
你閉嘴。
I'm arguing with her.
我正在和她爭論。
I'll be right back.
我馬上回來。
Okay.
好的。
So, how's the second greatest love affair of the century?
那麼，本世紀第二偉大的愛情故事怎麼樣呢？
The second?
第二個？
Who's the first?
誰是第一名？
Me and this muffin.
我和這個鬆餅。
My God, it's delicious.
天哪，真好吃。
So, how's it going with Joe?
那麼，喬的情況怎麼樣呢？
Uh, okay.
呃，好吧。
Okay.
好的。
Wait.
等待。
Okay.
好的。
Tell me.
告訴我。
Tell me that you like him, please.
請告訴我你喜歡他。
Tell me that you like him.
告訴我你喜歡他。
Look, he's a really great guy and I know that you really want
聽著，他是一個非常棒的人，我知道你真的想要
this to work out, but I just don't see this having a future.
這個解決方案，但我只是不認為它有未來。
But you said that you liked him.
但你說過你喜歡他。
I mean, what happened?
我的意思是，發生了什麼事？
Did you just change your mind?
你剛剛改變主意了嗎？
Kinda.
有點。
Then change it back!
那就改回來吧！
I'm sorry.
對不起。
It's just there's no real spark.
只是沒有真正的火花。
No spark?
沒有火花？
Didn't you sleep together?
你們沒一起睡嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Ah, tramp.
啊，流浪漢。
Does Joey have any idea?
喬伊有什麼想法嗎？
I really don't think he does.
我真的不認為他這樣做。
And you know what?
你知道嗎？
Maybe you guys could help clue him in.
也許你們可以幫他找出線索。
You know, tell him I'm not interested in a serious relationship or something.
你知道，告訴他我對認真的戀愛關係什麼的不感興趣。
Yeah, you mean like that you're kind of a loner?
是的，你的意思是說你是一個孤獨的人？
Yeah, that'd be great.
是的，那就太好了。
Yeah.
是的。
And maybe that you're a real stronzo?
也許你是真正的強者？
I'm sorry?
對不起？
Oh, well, I guess Italian isn't one of the four languages you speak.
哦，好吧，我想義大利語不是你說的四種語言之一。
Ready?
準備好？
Wanna go?
想去嗎？
Yeah, let's go.
是的，我們走吧。
Okay.
好的。
See you guys later.
稍後見。
Bye, Ben.
再見，本。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Wow.
哇。
Well, I guess it wasn't Cupid that brought her here.
嗯，我猜不是丘位元把她帶到這裡來的。
No, just a regular old flying dwarf.
不，只是一個普通的老飛行矮人。
Yes?
是的？
How can I help you?
我怎麼幫你？
We were just looking around.
我們只是四處看看。
Oh, you're fellow scholars.
呵呵，你們都是學者啊。
What exactly were you looking for?
您到底在尋找什麼？
Perhaps Dr. Chester Stock's musings on the Smilodon californicus?
也許是切斯特·斯托克博士對加州劍齒虎的思考？
Ah, get out of here!
啊，離開這裡！
Hi, meeting someone?
嗨，遇見某人了嗎？
Or are you just here to brush up on Merriam's views on evolution?
或者您只是來這裡溫習梅里亞姆的進化論觀點？
Um, actually, I find Merriam's views far too progressionist.
嗯，實際上，我發現梅里亞姆的觀點過於進步主義。
I find Merriam's views far too progressionist.
我發現梅里亞姆的觀點過於進步主義。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Who are you?
你是誰？
I'm a professor here.
我是這裡的教授。
Ross Geller.
羅斯蓋勒.
Ross Geller?
羅斯蓋勒？
Why do I know that name?
為什麼我知道這個名字？
It's a...
這是一個...
Wait.
等待。
Did you write this?
這是你寫的嗎？
Yes.
是的。
What?
什麼？
You're the person who checked out my book?
你就是那個看過我書的人嗎？
You know, you look nothing like I would have thought.
你知道，你看起來一點也不像我想象的那樣。
You're...
你是...
You're so young.
你還這麼年輕。
Well, I, uh...
嗯，我，呃...
I skipped fourth grade.
我跳過了四年級。
What?
什麼？
I am very, very sorry.
我非常非常抱歉。
Hey.
嘿。
Hi.
你好。
So, how was your day?
那麼，你今天過得怎麼樣呢？
It was great.
太棒了。
I mean, we walked all around the village.
我的意思是，我們繞著村子走了一圈。
We went to this ice cream place, split a milkshake.
我們去了這家冰淇淋店，分了一杯奶昔。
70-30, but still.
70-30，但仍然如此。
And guess what?
你猜怎麼著？
I'm thinking of taking her upstate to one of those bed-and-breakfasts.
我正在考慮帶她去州北部住一間提供民宿的旅館。
Oh, really?
哦真的嗎？
She said she wants to go away with you?
她說她想和你一起走？
No, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不。
It's a surprise.
這是一個驚喜。
It's gonna be tricky, though, because she said she's gonna be pretty busy
不過這會很棘手，因為她說她會很忙
at work for a while.
工作了一段時間。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
She said that?
她這麼說？
Yep.
是的。
Um, Joey, but don't you think maybe it's kind of quick for you
嗯，喬伊，但你不覺得這對你來說可能有點快嗎
to, you know, be going away together on a trip?
你知道，一起去旅行嗎？
Not for me.
不適合我。
No, I want to spend as much time with her as I can.
不，我想盡可能多地和她在一起。
Okay, honey, Joey, we need to talk, okay?
好吧，親愛的，喬伊，我們需要談談，好嗎？
Um, I kind of got the feeling from her today that, uh, she's
嗯，今天我從她那裡感覺到，呃，她是
not looking for a serious relationship.
不尋找認真的關係。
Where are you getting this?
你從哪裡得到這個？
Well, she told me.
嗯，她告訴我的。
She said she's kind of a loner.
她說她是一個孤獨的人。
Oh.
哦。
Joey...
喬伊...
No, hey, Rach, it's cool, you know.
不，嘿，瑞秋，這很酷，你知道。
I'm a loner, too, right?
我也是一個孤獨的人，對嗎？
Hey, Joey, you know what?
嘿，喬伊，你知道嗎？
You are way too good for her.
你對她來說太好了。
Yeah, and, honey, I promise, next time, I will just say goodbye and
是的，而且，親愛的，我保證，下次，我會說再見，
tell him you are not looking for a relationship.
告訴他你不是在尋找戀愛關係。
No.
不。
Don't do that.
不要那樣做。
Just...
只是...
Next time, make sure she really likes me.
下次，確保她真的喜歡我。
You know that, too.
你也知道這一點。
Joey?
喬伊？
Yeah?
是的？
Do you want some pancakes?
你想要一些煎餅嗎？
Finally.
最後。
What are we gonna do?
我們要做什麼？
I say we go with careless whisperer.
我說我們和粗心的竊竊私語者一起去。
Chandler?
錢德勒？
Did she see us yet?
她看到我們了嗎？
Did she see us?
Janice, what are you doing here?
珍妮絲，你在這裡做什麼？
Well, um, I thought I was gonna go back to my apartment, but
嗯，嗯，我以為我要回我的公寓，但是
then I just felt like I really couldn't be alone tonight.
然後我就覺得今晚我真的不能一個人待著。
I was just wondering if I could maybe stay here with you.
我只是想知道我是否可以留在這裡陪你。
Just, I really feel like I need to be with family.
只是，我真的覺得我需要和家人在一起。
My kids are gonna call her Aunt Janice, aren't they?
我的孩子會叫她珍妮絲阿姨，不是嗎？
Please.
請。
Otherwise, I really don't know what I might do.
不然我真的不知道自己會做什麼。
Aren't you just a teensy bit curious?
難道你就沒有一點點好奇嗎？
Do you have any tissues?
你有紙巾嗎？
Yeah, in the bathroom.
是的，在浴室裡。
Just let her stay.
就讓她留下來吧。
No, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不。
If we let her stay, she will stay forever.
如果我們讓她留下來，她就會永遠留下來。
I don't like your bark-a-lounder.
我不喜歡你大聲吠叫。
Is that what you're thinking about right now?
這就是你現在所想的嗎？
I never stop thinking about it.
我從未停止思考它。
What are we going to do?
我們要做什麼？
Nothing.
沒有什麼。
We just have to let her stay.
我們只能讓她留下來。
No, we can't.
不，我們不能。
We can't.
我們不能。
We gotta, we gotta fight.
我們必須，我們必須戰鬥。
We gotta, well, you tell me, we gotta fight.
我們必須，好吧，你告訴我，我們必須戰鬥。
Chandler, she has beaten me.
錢德，她打敗了我。
I'm tired, Chandler.
我累了，錢德勒。
So very tired.
所以很累。
Hey, you guys.
嘿，你們。
Um, do either one of you want to get in there before I
嗯，你們有人想在我之前進去嗎？
take my bath?
給我洗澡？
Janice, I'm sorry, but, uh, you can't stay here tonight.
珍妮絲，我很抱歉，但是，呃，你今晚不能留在這裡。
Why not?
為什麼不呢？
Honestly, our apartment is a hotbed for electromagnetic activity.
老實說，我們的公寓是電磁活動的溫床。
Now, Monica and I have been immunized, but sadly, you have not.
現在，莫妮卡和我已經接種疫苗，但遺憾的是，你還沒有。
Okay, I'm going to need a comforter.
好吧，我需要一個被子。
But do you have a hypoallergenic one?
但有防過敏的嗎？
Because otherwise I get very nasal.
因為否則我的鼻音就會變得很重。
Do you have a cat?
你有貓嗎？
Because it's already happening.
因為這已經發生了。
You hear that?
你聽到了嗎？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
You have to go.
你必須走了。
Why?
為什麼？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Because Chandler still has feelings for you.
因為錢德仍然對你有感覺。
She does?
她有嗎？
Say again?
再說一次？
That's right.
這是正確的。
And that is why you can't stay here tonight.
這就是為什麼你今晚不能留在這裡。
And probably why you shouldn't come to the wedding.
也許還有你不該參加婚禮的原因。
Feeling such strong feelings?
感受到如此強烈的感覺嗎？
I mean, I realize that his feelings may never completely go away, but
我的意思是，我意識到他的感情可能永遠不會完全消失，但是
you can.
你可以。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I understand.
我明白。
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉。
I'll go.
我去吧。
Goodbye, Monica.
再見，莫妮卡。
I wish you a lifetime of happiness with him.
祝你和他幸福一生。
Chandler, you call me when this goes in the pooper.
錢德勒，當這件事發生時你打電話給我。
Don't sweat it.
別出汗。
I got this section covered.
我已經涵蓋了這一部分。
In fact, I got this little baby to shine in people's eyes.
事實上，我讓這個小寶貝在人們眼中閃閃發光。
Okay, see you later.
好的，稍後見。
See you later.
稍後見。
I just wanted to show Monica your book.
我只是想給莫妮卡看你的書。